[Music]
[音乐]
this is Nick with logos by Nick comm and
我是尼克·康姆的标志尼克
in this tutorial I'll be demonstrating
在本教程中，我将演示
how you can create your own custom
如何创建您自己的定制
brushes in Inkscape and if you'd like to
在Inkscape中使用画笔，如果您愿意
learn more about how Inkscape works be
了解有关Inkscape如何工作的更多信息
sure to check out my Inkscape
一定要看看我的Inkscape
masterclass it's a collection of over 50
大师班，这是一个超过50件的收藏
videos where I go over all of the tools
我浏览了所有工具的视频
and features in Inkscape and I explain
和Inkscape中的功能，我解释
what they are and demonstrate how they
它们是什么并演示它们如何
work I'll have a link in the description
工作我会在描述中有一个链接
of the video if you want to check that
如果您想要查看视频
out so to get us started here in
所以让我们从这里开始
Inkscape the way that this works is
Inkscape的工作方式是
Inkscape doesn't actually have a brushes
Inkscape实际上没有画笔
feature built in but what it does have
内置功能，但它所具有的
is it has tools like the pencil tool
它有铅笔工具之类的工具吗？
over here which allow you to use a
在这里，允许您使用
custom shape based on what you have
根据您所拥有的内容自定义形状
copied to your clipboard and that's what
复制到你的剪贴板上，这就是
we'll be doing here so to show you an
我们将在这里为您展示一个
example of how this works I'm just gonna
这是一个工作原理的例子，我只想
create a square over here a regular
在这里创建一个正方形，一个普通的
perfectly symmetrical square like that
像这样完美对称的正方形
let me just convert this to a path by
让我通过以下方式将其转换为路径
going to path object to path let me
转到路径对象转到路径让我
scale that down I'm gonna right click
缩小比例，我要右键单击
this and I'm gonna go to copy and then
这个和我要去复印，然后
I'll come over here to the pencil tool
我到这儿来拿铅笔工具
and if you notice over here I have these
如果你注意到这里，我有这些
settings I'm using create regular Bezier
我正在使用的设置创建常规贝塞尔曲线
path the smoothing I'm gonna have that
路径，平滑，我要做的是
set to about 75 I'll explain that in a
设置为大约75，我将在
minute and where it says shape I'm gonna
分钟和它说的形状，我要
have this set to from a clipboard and if
将此设置为从剪贴板，并且如果
I click and drag on the canvas like that
我像这样在画布上点击并拖动
you'll notice what it basically do is it
你会注意到它的基本功能是
took that square and stretched it out
把那个正方形拉长了
along that path right here and if I go
沿着这条路走下去，如果我走了
to the edit pads by nodes tool you'll
要使用按结点编辑焊盘工具，您将
notice you'll get a little handle right
注意，你会得到一个正确的小把手
here and you can stretch out the width
在这里，你可以伸展一下宽度
of this path right here and you could
在这条小路上，你可以
even change the the path itself like how
甚至改变了道路本身，就像
it flows and everything like that so let
它流动着，一切都像那样，所以让
me get rid of this let me come back over
我摆脱这一切，让我回来吧
here to the pencil tool just to show you
这里的铅笔工具只是为了向你展示
something else here over here where it
这里有别的东西，在那里它
says smoothing this determines how rough
说平滑这决定了它有多粗糙
or how smooth the line that you create
或者你创造的这条线有多流畅
is if I bring this smoothing all the way
就是如果我把这种平滑带到
down to something like 10 and I leave it
降到10左右，然后我就离开了
there and then I go to create another
然后我就去创造另一个
line you'll notice it's a lot more a lot
你会注意到这条线要多得多
more of my hand tremors are reflected in
我的手更多的颤抖反映在
the the contour of that line right there
那条线的轮廓就在那里
now let me undo that if I bring the
现在让我撤销这一切，如果我把
smoothing up even higher if I bring it
如果我带上它，会变得更光滑
up too high to like maybe something like
太高了，可能不喜欢这样的东西
92 I'll go to create a curved line and
我要去画一条曲线，然后
won't curve as much as as I drew it
不会像我画的那样弯曲
it'll be nice and smooth but it'll be
它会很好很平稳，但它会
hard to get those real curves that you'd
很难得到真正的曲线，你会
like to draw in that line so I've found
喜欢画这条线，所以我找到了
that a good a good area is about 75 I
一个好的一个好的区域大约是75I
like to use about 75 that gives you a
我喜欢使用大约75，这给了你一个
nice fluid line without having any of
漂亮的液体管路，没有任何
the the rough shakes from from your hand
从你手中粗糙的颤抖
so let me take this get rid of this now
所以让我拿着这个，现在就把这个扔掉
let me show you how this can work with
让我向您展示这是如何与
like other custom shapes like stars I'm
像其他像星星一样的定制形状，我是
gonna create this star over here I'm
我要在这里创造出这颗星
gonna use a regular star instead of a
我会用普通的星星而不是
polygon I'm gonna use eight corners the
多边形，我要用八个角
spoke ratio is 0.75 and rounded and
轮辐比为0.75，四舍五入
randomized both set at zero and I'm
随机化，两者都设置为零，我
gonna click and drag on the camp so I'm
我会点击并拖拽营地，所以我
just gonna hold ctrl and shift so we
只需按住Ctrl键和Shift键，这样我们
create that star like that there we go
像这样创造那颗星，我们走吧
that's what I'm looking for and I'll go
这就是我要找的，我要走了
to path object to path to convert that
将对象路径设置为要转换的路径
to a path object and now I can grab the
到路径对象，现在我可以获取
Edit path by nodes tool and I'm just
按节点编辑路径工具，我只是
gonna click and drag over all of those
我会点击并拖动所有这些
nodes and click this little plus icon in
节点并在中单击此小加号图标
here to add some new nodes in there and
在此处添加一些新节点，并
then what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna go
然后我要做的就是我要去
to extensions modify path jitter nodes
修改路径抖动节点的扩展
and I have this set here to 3.0 and 3.0
我把这个设置为3.0和3.0
for both the X and y-axis the shift
对于X轴和Y轴，平移
nodes and shift handles both enabled and
节点和移位控制柄均已启用和
I'm gonna click on distribution we want
我要点击我们想要的分销
uniform I'm gonna click on live preview
制服，我要点击现场预览
just to see what that looks like and
只是想看看那是什么样子
that right there is what we're looking
这就是我们要找的东西
for like a like a rough kind of it kind
就像是一种粗暴的那种
of looks like an inkblot is what I'm
看起来就像是我的墨迹
looking for there I'm gonna click a pie
寻找那里，我会点击一个馅饼
and I'm actually gonna simplify this
我实际上会简化这一过程
path a little bit I'll go to path
小路，我要去小路
simplify or you can just press ctrl L
简化或只需按Ctrl键L
and you might want to click that a few
你可能想点击这几个
more times I'll try ctrl L a couple more
我会再试几次按Ctrl键控制L
times something like that looking pretty
像这样的东西看起来很漂亮
good now let me scale that down I'm
好的，现在让我缩小规模，我正在
gonna hold ctrl and shift and maintain
按住Ctrl键、Shift键并保持
the proportions and now I'm gonna copy
比例，现在我要复制
that to the clipboard by right-clicking
通过右键单击将其复制到剪贴板
it going to copy come back over here to
它会复制过来，回到这里来
the pencil tool or the draw freehand
铅笔工具或手绘
lines tool and then just click and drag
线工具，然后只需单击并拖动
on the canvas like that and you'll
在这样的画布上，你就会
notice it draws like this nice it looks
注意它是这样画的，看起来很漂亮
like a streak of paint now if you come
如果你来了，就像现在的一道油漆
back over here to the nodes tool you can
返回到此处的节点工具，您可以
change the thickness of this to make it
改变这个的厚度以使其成为
look even better like that and when
这样看起来更好，而且什么时候
you're drawing your lines let me come
你在划你的底线让我来
back over here to the tool if when
回到这里的工具，如果当
you're drawing your lines you're getting
你在画你得到的底线
like an outline with no fill you can
就像一个没有填充的轮廓，你可以
change the settings of that up here
在这里更改设置
where it says fill and Stroke you just
上面写着填充和击打你只需
click on that
点击该按钮
and it has the tool settings right here
它的工具设置就在这里
now I think by default that has this to
现在我认为这是默认的
this tool zone style and has that set by
此工具区域样式，并通过以下设置
default but I just changed it to this
默认设置，但我刚将其更改为
right here last use style so that's
就在这里最后使用的样式，所以这是
another feature you can work with a
您可以使用的另一个功能
little further here in Inkscape so I
在Inkscape这里稍远一点，所以我
think that should do it for this
我觉得这样就够了
tutorial
补习
oh wait you know what one more thing I
哦，等等，你知道我还有一件事
just want to show you once you're happy
只是想让你知道，一旦你开心了
with how your your your brushstroke
你的笔触是如何
looks what you can do is you can
看起来你能做的就是
finalize it by going to path object to
通过转到路径对象来完成它
path and now you can edit it and work
路径，现在您可以对其进行编辑和工作
with it like any other path oops it has
就像任何其他路径一样哎呀
individual nodes as you can see here so
正如您在这里看到的那样，所以
I think that should do it
我认为应该可以了
I think that should do it for this
我认为这应该就够了
tutorial if you
教程，如果您
[Music]
[音乐]